One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Hey, lackey!
!أيها التابع
The Stalwart War Spear
رمح الحرب الشعواء
Hang in there!
!تماسك
Now, breathe!
!هيا تنفس
Breathe in lots of good air!
!تنفس كثيرًا من الهواء النقي
Are you all right? Hey!
أأنت بخير؟
How about some water? Hey!
أتريد شرب قليلًا من الماء؟
This is bad.
هذا سيّئ
Do you wanna eat my special pudding?
أتريد أكل البودينغ الخاص الذي أعدُّه؟
It's good!
!إنه لذيذ
Idiot! You wanna feed poison to a poisoned man?!
!أتريد إطعام سمٍّ لرجلٍ مسمّم أيها الأحمق؟
Hey, what do you mean by poison?!
ماذا تقصد بسمّ؟
You're one to talk!
!أنت آخر من يتكلم
What'd you say?!
ماذا قلت؟
People say my meat dishes are the best in the world!
!يقول الناس أنّ أطباق اللحم خاصّتي الأفضل في العالم
They're good enough to die for!
!إنهم لذيذون حتى الموت
Don't die on us!
!لا تمت علينا
H-How's this fight gonna turn out?
مـ-ما الذي سيحدث لهذا القتال؟
Idiot! That was just dumb luck!
!أحمق، كان ذلك مجرّد حظ
A stupid brat could never defeat the don!
مستحيلٌ أن يهزم الدون ضد شقيٍّ مثله
Don't worry!
لا تقلق
Cabin Boy...
...أيها العامل
"I'm not gonna die here"... you say?
أقلتَ «لن أموتَ هُنا»؟
If you won't die here...
...إن كنتَ لن تموت هنا
then...
...فحينها
who the hell will?!
من سيموت إذًا؟
It'll be you, of course!
ألستَ أنت؟
No, it'll be you!
!بل أنت
The don was knocked down again!
!سقط الدون ثانية
What the hell is going on?!
!ما الذي يجري؟
O-Our enemies usually die before even touching Don Krieg...
...يُـ-يُفترض أن يموت الأعداء دون لمس الدون كريغ حتى
He's supposed to be invincible...
...يُفترض أنّ الدون لا يُقهر
What the...
...فما
What the hell is that brat?!
!فما قصّة ذلك الفتى؟
He's really good!
!إنّه بارع فعلًا
Yeah, I'm blown away...
نعم، أنا مندهش
He's amazing!
!إنه مذهل
Get that Krieg bastard!
!نِل من كريغ الوضيع
Yeah, he can do it!
!أجل، بإمكانه ذلك
That brat is actually going toe to toe with the don...
...يقاتل ذلك الفتى بنفس مستوى الدون دون أدنى شك
Is this a dream? The don's getting beat by someone like him...
...لا نحلم، صحيح؟ أن يُهزم الدون على يد فتًى مثله
The don's supposed to be invincible...
...يُفترض أنّ الدون لا يقهر
Don Krieg's legend as the greatest is about to be...
...على هذا الحال، فإن أسطورة الدون كريغ الأقوى سـ
Stop spouting nonsense!
!كفاكم تفوّهًا بالهراء
What the...
...ماذا
F-Finally...
...أ-أخيرًا، سلاح الدون كريغ الأقوى
The Stalwart War Spear!
!رمح الحرب الشعواء
What's that?
ما ذاك؟
It exploded.
انفجر
Now...
...والآن
Let's see how long you can run from this.
...لنرى إلى متى ستقدر على تفادي هجماتي
It'll be a sight, anchor boy.
ستمتعني بذلك أيها الفتى المرساة
While you may still be standing after a few hits from those puny stakes,
،ما زال بوسعك الوقوف بعد تلقيك لهجمات رماحي السابقة
the Stalwart Spear is different.
.لكنّ رمح الحرب الشعواء هذا مختلف
A single touch will blow you to bits!
!ستنفجر لأشلاء بمجرّد أن يلمسك
Wh-What's with that spear?!
مـ-ما ذلك الرمح؟
Don't fall, don't fall!
!سأسقط، سأسقط
There's an explosion with every hit?
أينفجر في كل مرة يضرب به؟
What? My knees...
...ماذا؟ ركبتاي
It'll be a problem if this fight drags on.
...ستكون المعركة الطويلة مشكلة
He's lost too much blood.
...نزف كثيرًا من الدماء
He won't last much longer...
...لن يصمد طويلًا
Your overexertion has taken its toll on you.
.مبالغتك عادت بالضرر عليك
You must be reaching your limit.
لا بدّ أنك استنزفتَ طاقتك
Dammit...
...سُحقًا
With the way it's rocking, I can't go all out.
لا أستطيع القتال بكامل قوّتي هكذا
I'm stumped.
...يا لهذه الورطة
The Stalwart War Spear never ceases to amaze me.
لا يكفّ رمح الحرب الشعواء ذاك عن إدهاشي
Yeah, the harder you slam that big spear down,
،نعم، كلّما كانت ضربة الرمح كبيرة
the bigger the explosion it causes.
.كان الانفجار الّذي يسبّبه أكبر
It's a weapon that only the don could possibly handle!
!لا يقدر أحدٌ غير الدون على تحمله
He's so powerful...
لكن ما مدى قوته؟
He's swinging around that heavy spear so easily...
لا أصدّق أنه يلوّح بذلك الرمح الثقيل بهذه السهولة
With those shoulder guards, it's gotta weigh at least a ton!
رغم أنّ وزنه طنٌّ كامل مع واقيتا الكتفين
That strength is exactly why nobody can match the don!
يُعدّ الدون الأقوى لذلك السبب تحديدًا
Take this!
!خذ هذه
Die!
!مُت
Cabin Boy!
!أيها العامل
That was close.
...كان ذلك وشيكًا
You...
!أيها الدودة اللعينة
Cabin Boy!
!أيها العامل
Cabin Boy...
...أيها العامل
I'm not done yet.
لم أكتفِ بعد
You've pissed me off.
فقد أغضبتني
I won't let you die so easily.
لن أدعك تموت بسهولة
Dammit!
!سُحقًا
That Krieg bastard pulls out weapons one after another...
يُخرج ذلك الوغد كريغ سلاحًا تلو الآخر
There's no way that cabin boy can...
...ليس بوسع العامل فعل شيءٍ هكذا
Even if you pierce his body with hundreds of weapons,
،مهما كثرت الأسلحة التي بحوزته
nobody stands a chance against a spear of blind determination.
يُمكن أن يُهزم على يد رجلٍ يتمتع بعزيمة عمياء متقدة
How easy...
هذا سهل
Now that makes you worth crushing.
يجعلك هذا جديرًا أن أسحقك
Life or death...
...الحياة أو الموت
In a battle between pirates, you'll fall apart if you fear death for even a moment.
في معركة قراصنة، إن خشيتَ الموت ولو للحظة، فستُهزم
What are you talking about?
عمّ تتحدّث؟
At least...
...على الأقل
that kid isn't showing...
...في ذلك الفتى
the smallest amount of hesitation!
!لا أرى ذرة تردّد
Is it a survival instinct?
أهي غريزة البقاء؟
Or does he not fear death due to his conviction?
أم أنه لا يخشى الموت لثقته في نفسه؟
Conviction...
...ثقة
Y-You son of a bitch!
!أ-أيها الوغد
Alright! You're amazing!
!ممتاز، أنت مذهل
Cabin Boy! Go for it!
!واصل أيها العامل
Get him!
!نلِ منه
I told you...
...أخبرتك
that this is where you die!
!ستموت هنا
I stand unparalleled!
!أنا الرجل الأقوى
The fleet that Krieg gathered... His hundreds of weapons and poisons...
الأسطول الذي جمعه كريغ بأسلحته وسمومه العديدة
If that's what power is...
إنّ كانت تلك كل قوته
then that kid's spear...
فعزيمة ذلك الفتى
is power as well.
تضاهيها قوّةً
The spear held in his heart.
عزيمةٌ يحملها في قلبه
I know an idiot who holds that spear back for no good reason.
أعرف غبيًّا يخفي عزيمةً مماثلة لسبب غبيّ
M-My Stalwart War Spear...
...ر-رمح الحرب الشعواء
What the hell did you do?!
!ما الذي فعلته؟
I punched it five times.
لكمتُه خمس لكمات
I guess that's it for your spear.
أظنّها نهاية رمحك
Get ready...
...استعدّ
I have enough room now to kick your ass!
بوسعي بطشك مع موطئ قدم بشطك
What?
ماذا؟
With the blade broken, that spear's just a bomb on a stick.
أصبح سلاحك مجرّد قنبلة على عصا بعد انكسار نصل الرمح
It's only half as strong.
خسر نصف قوّته
You think so?
أتعتقد ذلك؟
Yeah, I do.
نعم
A bomb on a stick?
قنبلة على عصا؟ وماذا في ذلك؟
Given the shape you're in, it's more than enough to blow you away.
نظرًا للحالة التي أنت فيها، فذلك أكثر من كافٍ لتفجيرك
With your body falling apart like that, anything you say just sounds like a bluff.
بما أنّ جسدك في حالة يُرثى لها، أرى كلّ ما تقوله محضّ خداعٍ
I'm not bluffing.
أنا لا أخادعك
That kid is pretty good.
ذلك الشقي بارع جدًا
He just might pull it off!
!قد يفعلها
This is bad...
...هذا سيئ
How did he break the Stalwart War Spear...?
كيف كسر رمح الحرب الشعواء...؟
But he's taken so many explosions...
بالمقابل، تضرّر كثيرًا من الانفجارات
His body can't keep up.
جسده لن يتحمل أكثر
Just give it up!
استسلم فحسب
The moment you defied Don Krieg,
،في اللحظة التي تحدّيتني فيها أنا
you signed your death warrant!
!وقّعتَ شهادة وفاتك
I won't die!
لن أموت
Hey! I'm over here!
أنا هنا
That monkey!
!يا لذلك القرد
He keeps swinging around!
!لا يكفّ عن القفز في الأرجاء
It's useless!
!لا فائدة
Just how many weapons does he have in there?!
!كم سلاحًا بحوزته بحق
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Gatling!
غاتلينغ
Weak!
!واهن
Your punches are powerless against this wootz steel armor!
لا قوّة للكماتك ضدّ درعي المصنوع من فولاذ ووتز
You can't even put a dent in it.
لا يمكنك خدشه حتى
Gum-Gum Pistol!
غومو غومو نو
Don!
!أيها الدون
How impudent!
!يا لوقاحتك
Useless! Useless! Utterly useless!
لا فائدة، لا فائدة، فلا فائدة من هذا
This armor won't break, even with hundreds of monkey punches!
لن ينكسر هذا الدرع وإن سدّدت له مئات من لكمات القرود هذه
I think I'm pretty close...
...أعتقد أنني وشيك
He's gone...
...اختفى
I'm right here!
!أنا هنا
Listen up.
،أنصت
Ultimate power is the result of advanced equipment wielded by the most strength.
القوة القصوى تعني المعدات الأقوى والقوة الأشد
The strong will always prevail.
،البقاء للأقوى
The strong!
!للأقوى
Then, that'd be me!
!سيكون ذلك أنا إذًا
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Useless! Useless! It's useless!
!لا فائدة! لا فائدة! لا فائدة
Stubbornness will only get you so far!
!حتى عنادك لن ينفعك طويلًا
Bazooka!
بازوكا
No good!
لا فائدة
This is all you can do!
هذا كلّ ما بوسعك فعله
What?! My invincible armor is cracking?!
ماذا؟ الدرع الأقوى يتصدّع؟
But it's too late.
لكن الأوان فات
You're done for, anchor boy!
انتهى أمرك أيها الفتى المرساة
It's a trap! Run!
!إنه فخ، اهرب
Cabin Boy!
!أيها العامل
Is it a survival instinct?
أهي غريزة البقاء؟
Or does he not fear death due to his conviction?
أم أنه لا يخشى الموت لثقته في نفسه؟
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
What?!
!ماذا؟
Bazooka!
بازوكا
All right!
!مرحى
Good job!
!أحسنت
You're the best, Cabin Boy!
!أنت الأفضل أيها العامل
I win!
!فزت
Don't get carried away, brat!
!يا لاستنتاجك الهرائي أيها الشقي
He's still alive!
!ما زال حيًّا
Uh oh!
!مصيبة
Let's see you escape this steel net!
!أيمكنك الهرب؟ أنها شبكة فولاذية
Below us is the ocean!
البحر تحتنا
It's over, anchor boy!
!انتهى القتال أيها الفتى المرساة
The last laugh belongs to me!
!أنا من سيضحك أخيرًا
Alright! That's our don!
!أجل، كما عهدنا من الدون
Drag him down!
!أسقطه
Get him!
!نِل منه
If I can get my arms and legs out, I win!
طالما أستطيع إخراج ذراعيّ وساقيّ فلم ينتهِ شيءٌ بعد
Why doesn't he falter?
لمَ لا يتراجع؟
Why does he go that far?
لمَ يتمادى لهذا الحدّ؟
What?!
ماذا؟
This is gonna end it...
...سأنهي الأمر بهذا
for sure!
!بالتأكيد
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Giant Hammer!
أوزوتشي
Don Krieg...
...الدون كريغ
The don... The don was defeated! How?!
الدون... هُزم الدون، لماذا؟
Dammit!
!سُحقًا
Alright, Cabin Boy!
!أحسنتَ أيها العامل
Dammit! How? How was the don...
...سحقًا، كيف؟ الدون
Good job!
!أحسنتَ عملًا
He really did it!
!هزمه فعلًا
A-Amazing!
!مـ-مذهل
Is this real?
أهذا حقيقيّ؟
This is Don Krieg we're talking about!
!نحن نتحدث عن الدون كريغ
So strong!
!إنّه قوي
He's unstoppable!
!إنه قوي لا يُقهر
Wh-What's all the fuss?
مـ-ما هذه الجلبة؟
Oh! You've come to!
!ها قد استيقظت
He lost!
!لقد خسر
Your don lost!
!خسر الدون خاصتكم
What?!
ماذا؟
Quit your daydreaming and save that kid already!
إن كان لديك وقت لأحلام اليقظة فاذهب لإنقاذ ذلك الفتى
He won't be floating back up!
لن يتمكن من الطفو
What?!
ماذا؟
Those with devil fruit powers are hated by the sea.
إن البحر يكره من يتمتع بقدرة فاكهة شيطان
They sink like an anchor.
فيفقدون القدرة على السباحة
What'd you say, you old fart?!
ماذا قلتَ أيها العجوز اللعين؟
You should've told me that sooner!
!كان عليك إخباري باكرًا
What are you gonna do if it's too late?!
ماذا ستفعل إن فات الأوان؟
Hey! Hang in there!
!أنت، تمالك نفسك
You said you wouldn't die, right?
قلتَ أنكَ لن تموت، صحيح؟
That's your conviction, right?!
ذلك ما تؤمن به، صحيح؟
Right?!
صحيح؟
I won't die!
!لن أموت
I'm not gonna die here.
لن أموت هنا
Really, these guys...
...بحق
Zoro!
!زورو
Dying is worse than giving up his ambition!
كان عليه أن يتخلى عن طموحه بدلًا عن الموت
The choice was easy!
ألم يكن التخلي عن طموحك سهلًا؟
Every single one of them...
...جميعهم
I don't know why, but...
...لا أدري لماذا، لكن
if I withdraw even one step,
،إن تراجعتُ ولو خطوة واحدة
it feels as if all the important oaths and promises that I once made will shatter,
أشعر وكأنّ أمورًا عديدة مثل الوعود والعهود ستتحطم
and I won't be able to come back to where I am now.
...ولن أعود قادرًا على الرجوع إلى حيث أنا الآن
Nobody stands a chance against a spear of blind determination.
يُمكن أن يُهزم على يد رجلٍ يتمتع بعزيمة عمياء متقدة
I know an idiot who holds that spear back for no good reason.
أعرف غبيًّا يخفي عزيمةً مماثلة لسبب غبيّ
Hey, Cabin Boy!
!أيها العامل
Don't you die on me!
!إيّاك الموت
Don! What's the matter?!
ما الخطب أيها الدون؟
Why was the don...?
...لماذا الدون
Don!
!الدون
Don Krieg has been defeated...
...هُزم الدون كريغ
That can't be true...
...هذا مُحال
He's the conqueror of the East Blue...
...إنّه المُهيمن على الأزرق الشرقي
Even if you say so...
...حتى إن قلتَ ذلك
just take a look at him!
!ألقِ نظرةً وستصدّق
His prized armor got shattered, and he's out cold.
تحطّم درعه الّذي افتخر به وهو مغشيّ عليه الآن
He got beat good. Don't you wanna see?
هُزم شرّ هزيمة، ألن ترى ذلك؟
He's the only man I ever admired...
...الرجل الوحيد الذي تطلّعتُ له
I thought no one could rival him!
!آمنتُ أنه الأقوى
Hey wait, lackey!
!مهلًا أيها التابع
If you move, the poison will circulate!
إن تحركت الآن فسيقضي السمّ على جسمك
Sit still!
!لا تتحرك
I'm saying this for your own good!
!هذا لمصلحتك
Hey! You're gonna die!
!مهلًا! ستموت
Cabin Boy!
!أيها العامل
Don't die!
!لا تمت
Can you hear me?!
أتسمعني؟
You still have things to do, right?!
ما زالت لديك أمور لتفعلها، صحيح؟
Cabin Boy! Don't die!
!لا تمت أيها العامل
You're such a...
...أنت
You're really something...
...إنك لا تُصدّق
I'm the strongest!
!أنا الأقوى
I'll... I'll win!
!أنا... أنا الفائز
No one can surpass my power!
!لا أحد بإمكانه هزيمة قوّتي
Don! Please stop!
!توقف رجاءً أيها الدون
Hold him down! He's not even conscious!
!اكبحوا جماحه، ما زال فاقدًا لوعيه
I'll win!
!سأفوز
Please stop, Don!
!توقف أيها الدون
I'll win with my own might!
!سأفوز، باستعمال قوتي
I...
...عليّ
have to...
...أن
win!
!أفوز
Nobody can defeat me!
!أنا الرجل الأقوى
Don Krieg...
...أيها الدون كريغ
We lost.
خسرنا
– Commander!
!أيها القائد
Let's withdraw gracefully and start anew.
لننسحب بهدوء ونبدأ من الصفر
Thanks for everything, Sanji.
شكرًا على كل شيء يا سانجي-سان
Sure.
العفو
Don't ever come back!
لا تعُد أبدًا
Sanji,
...يا سانجي-سان
when he wakes up, please tell him I said...
...أخبره بهذا حين يستيقظ
"I'll see you again on the Grand Line."
سنلتقي ثانيةً في الغراند لاين
You...
...أنت
When I think about it carefully,
عند التفكير مليًّا
that's the only thing I want to do...
...أجد هذا الأمر الوحيد الذي أريد فعله
It seems that somewhere along the way, Don Krieg's ambition became my own.
أرى أنّ طموح الدون كريغ صار طموحي أيضًا قبل أن أدرك
I might...
...ربما
only have a few more hours left in me...
سأتمكّن من العيش لبضع ساعات أخرى
It's kinda stupid that I've resolved myself without the time left to use it,
من الغباء أنني عازم لأنني لا أملك الكثير من الوقت
but this time, I want to do things on my own terms...
لكن هذه المرة، أريد خوض الأمر بإرادتي
in my own way...
...وبطريقتي
In that case, there'd be nowhere for me to run, right?
وحينها، لن يعود لي مهرب، صحيح؟
To hell with loyalty to the don.
ما ولاء الدون هذا؟
I've just been running, using Don Krieg's name as a shield.
...كنتُ أهرب متدرّعًا باسم الدون كريغ فحسب
Once you're resolved, you don't have to think about worthless things
بمجرّد أن يعقد المرء العزم، لا يضطرّ للتفكير في أمور غبيّة
like fearing your enemy, or keeping yourself safe.
مثل الخوف من العدوّ أو كيف يتفادى التعرض للأذى
He taught me that.
.تعلّمتُ ذلك منه
Patty! Carne!
!باتي، كارني
Give him our grocery shopping boat!
!أعطوه القارب الذي نستعمله للتسوق
What?! Have you lost it?!
ماذا؟ أأنت أحمق؟
Why do we have to give our boat to pirates of all people?!
لماذا علينا إعطاء قاربنا لقراصنة؟
What are we gonna use for our grocery shopping?! You idiot!
كيف سنتسوق أيها الأحمق؟
He's right!
!معه حق
Let those guys swim!
!دعهم يسبحون
Just bring it out already!
!أحضراه فحسب
Okay, fine...
...فهمنا
Don't yell at us...
...لا تصرخ علينا
– Okay, okay, we'll bring it out!
!حسنًا، حسنًا، سنحضره
It's gonna sink!
!سيغرق
Why did I hesitate? What was I so worried about?
لماذا تردّدتُ؟ ما الذي قلقتُ بشأنه؟
When I think back on it, I feel like an idiot.
أشعر أنه أمر غبيّ عندما أفكر فيه
Well, then!
!مع السلامة
We gratefully accept the boat.
شكرًا على القارب
We don't have to return it, right?
ليس علينا إعادته، صحيح؟
Right.
صحيح
If you have the courage to return it, you can go ahead and try, small fry.
إن كانت لديك الشجاعة لتعيده فحاول ذلك أيها الضعيف
He's right!
!معه حق
Just keep this in your brain:
:اغرس هذا في عقلك
This is the Sea Restaurant, the fighting, floating Baratie!
!هذا مطعم باراتي القتالي البحري
– Yeah!
!أجل
What a scary restaurant.
...يا له من مطعم مخيف